<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Built-in tools on MsBullet</title><link>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/</link><description>Recent content in Built-in tools on MsBullet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coverlet</title><link>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/coverletmsbuild/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/coverletmsbuild/</guid><description>Coverlet. # This framework is provided as a built-in tool of MsBullet SDK to collect coverage through coverlet.msbuild.
How to use and customization. # By default, all projects that have the IsTestProject property set to true collect coverage metrics.
NOTE
To customize this tool, you can refer to the official repository Property Description Default value Overridable Note CoverletOutput Specifies the file path where the coverage report will be saved.</description></item><item><title>ReportGenerator</title><link>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/reportgenerator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/reportgenerator/</guid><description>ReportGenerator. # ReportGenerator is provided as a built-in tool of MsBullet SDK to generate code coverage reports.
How to use and customization. # By default, all projects that have the IsTestProject property set to true produce a human-readable report over collected coverage metrics by coverlet.
In addition, we produce a summary report that contains all cross-project collected metrics after each project test.
NOTE
To customize this tool, you can refer to the official site.</description></item><item><title>SonarSource Analyzer</title><link>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/sonaranalyzer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/sonaranalyzer/</guid><description>SonarSource Analyzer. # This analyzer is provided as a built-in tool of MsBullet SDK to help developers maintain high security and code quality.
How to use and customization. # By default, there is no application of specific configurations within the SDK.
NOTE
For customization of the rules of this tool, you can refer to the official repository Property Description Default value Overridable Note SonarAnalyzerCSharpVersion Set the tool version, by default it use the latest available major.</description></item><item><title>StyleCop Analyzers</title><link>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/stylecopanalyzers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binick.github.io/msbullet/configuration/tools/stylecopanalyzers/</guid><description>StyleCop Analyzers. # This analyzer is provided as a built-in tool of MsBullet SDK to enforce standard code conventions
How to use and customization. # By default, there is no application of specific configurations within the SDK.
NOTE
For customization of the rules of this tool, you can refer to the official documentation Property Description Default value Overridable Note StyleCopConfig Specifies the file path of stylecop.</description></item></channel></rss>